
exports.seed = function(knex, Promise) {
  return knex.raw('TRUNCATE TABLE questions CASCADE')
    .then(function () {
      return Promise.all([
        /*ALL QUESTIONS from http://www.w3resource.com/javascript-exercises/javascript-functions-exercises.php */
        knex('questions').insert({ id: 1001,
                                   question: "Write a JavaScript function that reverse a number.",
                                   example: "\/*\r\n\r\nExample:\r\n\r\nreverse_a_number(1234567890);\r\n\r\nExpected output:\r\n=> \'0987654321\'\r\n\r\n*\/",
                                   placeholder: "function reverse_a_number(n) {\r\n  \/* Put your code here*\/\r\n\r\n}",
                                   answer: "function reverse_a_number(n) {\r\n  n += \'\';\r\n  return n.split(\'\').reverse().join(\'\');\r\n}",
                                   unit_test: "reverse_a_number(1234567890);",
                                   test_result: "'0987654321'",
                                   language_id: 1,
                                   title: "Reverse the Number",
                                   difficulty: 1}),
        knex('questions').insert({ id: 1002,
                                   question: "Write a JavaScript function that returns a passed string with letters in alphabetical order.",
                                   example: "\/*\r\n\r\nExample:\r\nalphabet_order(\'webmaster\');\r\n\r\nExpected Output: \r\n=> \'abeemrstw\'\r\n\r\n*\/",
                                   placeholder: "function alphabet_order(str) {\r\n  \/* Put your code here *\/\r\n\r\n}",
                                   answer: "function alphabet_order(str) {\r\n  return str.split(\'\').sort().join(\'\');\r\n}",
                                   unit_test: "alphabet_order('webmaster');",
                                   test_result: "abeemrstw",
                                   language_id: 1,
                                   title: "Returns a passed string with letters in alphabetical order",
                                   difficulty: 1 }),
        knex('questions').insert({ id: 1003,
                                   question: "Write a JavaScript function that accepts a number as a parameter and check the number is prime or not.\n\nNote : A prime number (or a prime) is a natural number greater than 1 that has no positive divisors other than 1 and itself.",
                                   example: "\/*\r\n\r\nExample:\r\ntest_prime(37);\r\n\r\nExpected Output: \r\n=> true\r\n\r\n*\/",
                                   placeholder: "function test_prime(n) {\r\n  \/* Put your code here *\/\r\n\r\n}",
                                   answer: "function test_prime(n) {\r\n  if (n === 1) {\r\n    return false;\r\n  } else if (n === 2) {\r\n    return true;\r\n  } else {\r\n    for(var x = 2; x < n; x++) {\r\n      if(n % x === 0) {\r\n        return false;\r\n      }\r\n    }\r\n  return true;  \r\n  }\r\n}",
                                   unit_test: "test_prime(37);",
                                   test_result: "true",
                                   language_id: 1,
                                   title: "Check a number is prime or not",
                                   difficulty: 1 })
        // knex('questions').insert({ id: 1004,
        //                            question: "Sort the array from biggest to smallest",
        //                            answer: "answer4",
        //                            unit_test: "testing4",
        //                            language_id: 3,
        //                            title: "array sorting",
        //                            difficulty: 1 }),
        // knex('questions').insert({ id: 1005,
        //                            question: "Write a function blah blah",
        //                            answer: "answer5",
        //                            unit_test: "testing5",
        //                            language_id: 1,
        //                            title: "function",
        //                            difficulty: 1 }),
        // knex('questions').insert({ id: 1006,
        //                            question: "Make a function that multiplies two number together",
        //                            example: "\/*\r\n\r\nExample:\r\nalphabet_order(\'webmaster\');\r\n\r\nExpected Output: \r\n=> \'abeemrstw\'\r\n\r\n*\/",
        //                            placeholder: "function reverse_a_number(n) {\r\n  \/* Put your code here*\/\r\n\r\n}",
        //                            answer: "answer1",
        //                            unit_test: "testing1",
        //                            test_result: "'0987654321'",
        //                            language_id: 1,
        //                            title: "calculator",
        //                            difficulty: 2}),
        // knex('questions').insert({ id: 1007,
        //                            question: "Output track 1",
        //                            answer: "answer2",
        //                            unit_test: "testing2",
        //                            language_id: 2,
        //                            title: "music library",
        //                            difficulty: 3 }),
        // knex('questions').insert({ id: 1008,
        //                            question: "Find the smallest and second smallest integer",
        //                            answer: "answer3",
        //                            unit_test: "testing3",
        //                            language_id: 1,
        //                            title: "array length",
        //                            difficulty: 3 }),
        // knex('questions').insert({ id: 1009,
        //                            question: "Sort the array from biggest to smallest",
        //                            answer: "answer4",
        //                            unit_test: "testing4",
        //                            language_id: 3,
        //                            title: "array sorting",
        //                            difficulty: 3 }),
        // knex('questions').insert({ id: 1010,
        //                            question: "Write a function blah blah",
        //                            answer: "answer5",
        //                            unit_test: "testing5",
        //                            language_id: 1,
        //                            title: "function",
        //                            difficulty: 3 })
      ]);
    });
};
